<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<phrases>
	<phrase id="1">A star shines on the hour of our meeting.</phrase>
	<phrase id="2">In a hole in the ground there lived a hobbit.</phrase>
	<phrase id="3">Thinking furiously! Such is the vastness of his genius that he can outwit even himself.</phrase>
	<phrase id="4">When one does not know what one seeks, caution is the surest armour.</phrase>
	<phrase id="5">Don't rush me sonny, you rush a miracle man, you get rotten miracles.</phrase>
	<phrase id="6">The frog atop the stack of coins dares not jump.</phrase>
	<phrase id="7">So comes snow after fire, and even dragons have their endings.</phrase>
	<phrase id="8">Even the smallest person can change the course of the future.</phrase>
	<phrase id="9">The wide world is all about you: you can fence yourselves in, but you cannot forever fence it out.</phrase>
	<phrase id="10">Deeds will not be less valiant because they are unpraised.</phrase>
	<phrase id="11">I must not fear. Fear is the mind-killer. Fear is the little-death that brings total obliteration.</phrase>
	<phrase id="12">I will face my fear. I will permit it to pass over me and through me.</phrase>
	<phrase id="13">And when it has gone past I will turn the inner eye to see its path.</phrase>
	<phrase id="14">Where the fear has gone there will be nothing. Only I will remain.</phrase>
	<phrase id="15">A popular man arouses the jealousy of the powerful.</phrase>
	<phrase id="16">Parting with friends is a sadness. A place is only a place.</phrase>
	<phrase id="17">When religion and politics ride in the same cart, the whirlwind follows.</phrase>
	<phrase id="18">We tend to become like the worst in those we oppose.</phrase>
	<phrase id="19">Just as individuals are born, mature, breed, and die, so do societies and civilizations and governments.</phrase>
	<phrase id="20">You'd be amazed how much research you can get done when you have no life whatsoever.</phrase>
	<phrase id="21">One person can keep a secret, but not two.</phrase>
	<phrase id="22">You are what you do when it counts.</phrase>
	<phrase id="23">Life without any wonder left in it is flat and stale.</phrase>
	<phrase id="24">The sun stooped to the western waves, entering his bath of blood-red fire. He sank, and all the ways were darkened.</phrase>
	<phrase id="25">Lightning shall be slow to my hasting.</phrase>
	<phrase id="26">Drunkenness is better for the body than medicine! Drink always, and you shall never die!</phrase>
	<phrase id="27">Perhaps if you know you are insane then you are not insane. Or you are becoming sane, finally. Waking up.</phrase>
	<phrase id="28">We are all insects. Groping towards something terrible or divine.</phrase>
	<phrase id="29">What profit it a man if he gain the whole world but in this enterprise lose his soul?</phrase>
	<phrase id="30">Philosophical involvement blinded me to authentic human fact.</phrase>
	<phrase id="31">It's the basic condition of life to be required to violate our own identity.</phrase>
	<phrase id="32">My schedule for today lists a six-hour self-accusatory depression.</phrase>
	<phrase id="33">Owning and maintaining a fraud had a way of gradually demoralizing one.</phrase>
	<phrase id="34">You don't have to burn books to destroy a culture. Just get people to stop reading them.</phrase>
	<phrase id="35">There is more than one way to burn a book. And the world is full of people running about with lit matches.</phrase>
	<phrase id="36">If you hide your ignorance, no one will hit you and you'll never learn.</phrase>
	<phrase id="37">We are an impossibility in an impossible universe.</phrase>
	<phrase id="38">Your intuition knows what to write, so get out of the way.</phrase>
	<phrase id="39">A just universe wouldn’t tolerate my existence.</phrase>
	<phrase id="40">Will covers a multitude of flaws, just as love covers a multitude of sins.</phrase>
	<phrase id="41">It occurs to me that our survival may depend upon our talking to one another.</phrase>
	<phrase id="42">In such seconds of decision entire futures are made.</phrase>
	<phrase id="43">The shortest route to courage is absolute ignorance.</phrase>
	<phrase id="44">I loved you backward and forward in time. I loved you beyond boundaries of time and space.</phrase>
	<phrase id="45">Mobs have passions, not brains.</phrase>
	<phrase id="46">It no longer matters who consider themselves the masters of events.</phrase>
	<phrase id="47">Just because you have the emotional range of a teaspoon doesn’t mean we all have.</phrase>
	<phrase id="48">It does not do well to dwell on dreams and forget to live.</phrase>
	<phrase id="49">Fear of a name only increases fear of the thing itself.</phrase>
	<phrase id="50">I solemnly swear I am up to no good.</phrase>
	<phrase id="51">Jump, and you will find out how to unfold your wings as you fall.</phrase>
	<phrase id="52">There are worse crimes than burning books. One of them is not reading them.</phrase>
	<phrase id="53">The darkest places in hell are reserved for those who maintain their neutrality in times of moral crisis.</phrase>
	<phrase id="54">If we don't believe in freedom of expression for people we despise, we don't believe in it at all.</phrase>
	<phrase id="55">A fight is not won by one punch or kick. Either learn to endure or hire a bodyguard.</phrase>
	<phrase id="56">Art calls for complete mastery of techniques, developed by reflection within the soul.</phrase>
	<phrase id="57">Defeat is a state of mind; no one is ever defeated until defeat has been accepted as a reality.</phrase>
	<phrase id="58">Empty your cup so that it may be filled; become devoid to gain totality.</phrase>
	<phrase id="59">Notice that the stiffest tree is most easily cracked, while the bamboo or willow survives by bending with the wind.</phrase>
	<phrase id="60">A goal is not always meant to be reached, it often serves simply as something to aim at.</phrase>
	<phrase id="61">A wise man can learn more from a foolish question than a fool can learn from a wise answer.</phrase>
	<phrase id="62">Use only that which works, and take it from any place you can find it.</phrase>
	<phrase id="63">For it is easy to criticize and break down the spirit of others, but to know yourself takes a lifetime.</phrase>
	<phrase id="64">A quick temper will make a fool of you soon enough.</phrase>
	<phrase id="65">In the middle of chaos lies opportunity.</phrase>
	<phrase id="66">A good teacher protects his pupils from his own influence.</phrase>
	<phrase id="67">Everything you do, if not in a relaxed state will be done at a lesser level than you are proficient.</phrase>
	<phrase id="68">If you love life, don’t waste time, for time is what life is made up of.</phrase>
	<phrase id="69">Man, the living creature, the creating individual, is always more important than any established style or system.</phrase>
	<phrase id="70">The knowledge and skills you have achieved are meant to be forgotten so you can float comfortably in emptiness, without obstruction.</phrase>
	<phrase id="71">Don’t get set into one form, adapt it and build your own, and let it grow, be like water.</phrase>
	<phrase id="72">Mistakes are always forgivable, if one has the courage to admit them.</phrase>
	<phrase id="73">Those who are unaware they are walking in darkness will never seek the light.</phrase>
	<phrase id="74">No mule can match wits with me. Oh yes, many have tried, and almost all have failed!</phrase>
	<phrase id="75">We are history relived and this is all, without end that is all.</phrase>
	<phrase id="76">Of all the weapons we choose to turn upon ourselves, guilt is the sharpest.</phrase>
	<phrase id="77">Courting is the art of growing like mould on the one you want.</phrase>
	<phrase id="78">When you've burned the bridges behind you, don't go starting a fire on the one in front of you.</phrase>
	<phrase id="79">Discipline is as much facing the enemy within as the enemy before you.</phrase>
	<phrase id="80">It's easy to weep when staying far away, doing nothing.</phrase>
	<phrase id="81">We talk of progress, but what we really desire is the perpetuation of the present.</phrase>
	<phrase id="82">Those who knew but one path would come to worship it, even as it led to a cliff's edge.</phrase>
	<phrase id="83">The man patrolling his prejudices never sleeps.</phrase>
	<phrase id="84">The dust dreams of the world it had once been. But the dust, alas, does not command the wind.</phrase>
	<phrase id="85">Compassion is priceless in the truest sense of the word. It must be given freely. In abundance.</phrase>
	<phrase id="86">The heart is neither given nor stolen. The heart surrenders.</phrase>
	<phrase id="87">The lesson of history is that no one learns.</phrase>
	<phrase id="88">Wise words are like arrows flung at your forehead. What do you do? Why, you duck of course.</phrase>
	<phrase id="89">Regrets are as nothing. Their value lies in how they are answered.</phrase>
	<phrase id="90">The future can ever promise but one thing and one thing only: surprises.</phrase>
	<phrase id="91">No tyrant could thrive where every subject said no. The tyrant thrives when the first fool salutes.</phrase>
	<phrase id="92">The soul knows no greater anguish than to take a breath that begins with love and ends with grief.</phrase>
	<phrase id="93">Take care of the people, and god almighty will take care of himself.</phrase>
	<phrase id="94">I was a victim of a series of accidents, as are we all.</phrase>
	<phrase id="95">The Earthlings behaved at all times as though there were a big eye in the sky—as though that big eye were ravenous for entertainment.</phrase>
	<phrase id="96">There is room enough for an awful lot of people to be right about things and still not agree.</phrase>
	<phrase id="97">Always forgive your enemies; nothing annoys them so much.</phrase>
	<phrase id="98">Do not seek to follow in the footsteps of the men of old; seek what they sought.</phrase>
	<phrase id="99">We are what we repeatedly do; excellence, then, is not an act but a habit.</phrase>
	<phrase id="100">The crowd, having been promised nothing, felt cheated, having received nothing.</phrase>
	<phrase id="101">Hello ladies. You don't know me, but tomorrow you are going to miss me.</phrase>
</phrases>
